[
  {
    "question": "What house is Harry Potter in?",
    "choices": "  A - Gryffindor\n  B - Ravenclaw\n  C - Hufflepuff\n  D - Slytherin",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Harry Potter's wand core?",
    "choices": "  A - Dragon heartstring\n  B - Phoenix feather\n  C - Unicorn string",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry's best friend",
    "choices": "  A - Neville\n  B - Hermione\n  C - Ron\n  D - Ginny",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Harry's enemy at school?",
    "choices": "  A - Crabbe\n  B - Goyle\n  C - Dean\n  D - Malfoy",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What made Voldemort immortal and inhuman?",
    "choices": "  A - Totems of Undying\n  B - Unicorn blood\n  C - Horcruxes\n  D - The Philosopher's Stone",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Harry manage to breathe underwater during the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "choices": "  A - Bubblehead charm\n  B - Gillyweed\n  C - Transfigures into a shark",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Fred and George’s joke shop?",
    "choices": "  A - Weasley Joke Emporium\n  B - Zonko’s Joke Shop\n  C - Weasleys’ Wizard Wheezes",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is NOT one of the Unforgivable Curses?",
    "choices": "  A - Sectumsempra\n  B - The Cruciatus curse\n  C - Avada kedavra",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {"question": "Who guards the entrance to the Gryffindor common room?",
    "choices": "  A - The Grey Lady\n  B - The Fat Friar\n  C - The Fat Lady",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the spell \'Obliviate\' do?",
    "choices": "  A - Destroys objects\n  B - Makes objects invisible\n  C - Removes parts of someone’s memory",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Hermione brew her first batch of Polyjuice Potion?",
    "choices": "  A - The Room of Requirement\n  B - Moaning Myrtle's bathroom\n  C - The Gryffindor Common Room",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does one say to close the Marauder\'s Map and make it blank again?",
    "choices": "  A - Mischief Managed\n  B - All Done\n  C - Nothing to See Here",
    "answer": "a"
  }
]